<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simple Components on Dewey design system</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Simple Components on Dewey design system</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accordions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/accordions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/accordions/</guid>
      <description>Accordions Accordions can be a useful tool in dividing and segmenting information, if used judiciously. The design system features three variants, the transcript variant is used to provide accessible content for videos and images, the navigation option (featured on the right) allows for collapsible navigation.&#xA;Default Each accordion item is controlled by the user, they decide when each item opens and closes. While there is facility to have an accordion item open by default (see bootstrap docs), this begs the question, &#34;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockquotes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/blockquotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/blockquotes/</guid>
      <description>Blockquotes The Dewey design system is built using the Bootstrap 5 framework. As such, the system employs the following default bootstrap breakpoints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buttons</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/buttons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/buttons/</guid>
      <description>Buttons Two different varieties of button are available in the design system. Default state The button state hews closely to Bootstrap&#39;s btn-outline-secondary style. When multiple buttons are used on a page, almost all of them should in this style.&#xA;Default button Default button &amp;lt;button class=&amp;quot;btn btn-outline-secondary&amp;quot;&amp;gt;Button label&amp;lt;/button&amp;gt; or simply &amp;lt;button&amp;gt;Button label&amp;lt;/button&amp;gt; Primary button This style should be used sparingly, ideally only one occurrence on each page. It should action something important, like submitting a form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/dewey-design/components-simple/images/</guid>
      <description>Images Dewey offers various options in displaying images including borders, alignment, sizing and adding captions and transcript accordions. Markup For images used in page content, wrap all &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; tags in a &amp;lt;figure&amp;gt; tag. Remember to include an alt tag.&#xA;&amp;lt;figure&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=&amp;rdquo;my-image.jpg&amp;rdquo; alt=&amp;rdquo;An example image&amp;rdquo; / &amp;gt; &amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt; Spacing By default, each image has a margin of space-large applied top and bottom&#xA;Border Add a border to your image using the class border.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
